{
    "subject": "resource/RocknRolla",
    "predicate": "property/studio",
    "object": "resource/Dark_Castle_Entertainment",
    "human_readable": "RocknRolla was produced by Dark Castle Entertainment.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8193830251693726,
            "question": "What movie was produced by Dark Castle Entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7409552931785583,
            "question": "Who produced the film RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7363726496696472,
            "question": "Is Dark Castle Entertainment known for producing action films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6825109124183655,
            "question": "What other movies has Dark Castle Entertainment produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49670910835266113,
            "question": "Who directed RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47089534997940063,
            "question": "What year was RocknRolla released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4534686505794525,
            "question": "What genre is RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30217188596725464,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26877230405807495,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24970917403697968,
            "question": "Where can I watch RocknRolla?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RocknRolla was produced by Dark Castle Entertainment.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2745_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the plot of RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2745_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels to RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2745_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2745_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2745_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because according to the provided context information, it is stated that \"Starting with RocknRolla...the company began producing films in genres other than horror.\" (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2745/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt) and also \"RockNRolla\" is mentioned as one of the films produced by Dark Castle Entertainment (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2745/re-ranker-msmarco/122.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which state that Dark Castle Entertainment produced films including RocknRolla."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}